http://essexparts.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Essex Parts Services, Inc.
Company InformationOur TeamAftermarket ProductsAll ProductsNew ProductsClearance ItemsServicesRacing SeriesLate Model and ModifiedsNASCAR Cup SeriesIndyCarTCR / Touring CarSupportProduct Technical SupportOrdering, Shipping, ReturnsOrder TrackingLearning Center & FAQInternational OrdersMedia CenterPhoto GalleryVideo GalleryNews & BlogDealer Locator
Call: 704-824-6030
My Account
My Shopping Cart ( 0 )
Checkout
Wholesaler Quick Buy
Company InformationOur TeamAftermarket ProductsAll ProductsNew ProductsClearance ItemsServicesRacing SeriesLate Model and ModifiedsNASCAR Cup SeriesIndyCarTCR / Touring CarSupportProduct Technical SupportOrdering, Shipping, ReturnsOrder TrackingLearning Center & FAQInternational OrdersMedia CenterPhoto GalleryVideo GalleryNews & BlogDealer Locator
Wholesaler Quick Buy
Call: 704-824-6030
Select Your Vehicle:
Year
Aftermarket Calipers
2020
2019
2018
2017
2016
2015
Privacy Policy
ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS. By using this site, you agree to all terms, conditions, and notices
contained or referenced in these "Terms and Conditions of Usage”. Essex Parts reserve the right, to update or revise these Terms and
Conditions of Use at any time.
By using the Essex Parts
website you agree not to use this site for any unlawful purpose and
accept the risk of working on an open network. Although Essex Parts does not share personal information (Data and facts) they
cannot accept responsibility for any communications which may be
intercepted or do not reach the intended customer safely.
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY. By
using this site you agree and acknowledge that the trademarks, images,
text, design and layout are owned or licensed by Essex Parts.
(Trademarks which are not owned or licensed by Essex Parts are
represented on the site) and are protected by international and US
copyright regulation. Essex Parts graphics and logos are the sole
property of the website proprietor and use is only permitted with
express written permission by its owners. Hyperlinks used on
this site may redirect you to other sites (manufacturer’s websites).
Essex Parts cannot guarantee the accuracy of those hyperlinks or
associated websites in any respect. INDEMNIFICATION. By
using this site you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Essex Parts, its affiliated companies, partners, contractors, officers
and directors from all claims and expenses, including and not limited to
attorney fees that arise from the misuse of this site. Essex Parts reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the
exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to
indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate with Essex Parts in asserting any available defenses. PRIVACY POLICY. Essex Parts considers your privacy with the utmost importance. To
purchase products on this website it is necessary to collect and use
your personal information. Essex Parts do not share this
information with any third party without the express permission of the
customer. We may use this information to send customers offers, contest
or promotions usually by email. Essex Parts may also use your
purchasing information for sales analysis. However Essex Parts
does not accept responsibility for activities that occur from your
computer. It is your responsibility to control access to your account or
password. On every communication sent by Essex Parts there will be an option to unsubscribe. INTERNATIONAL USE. Essex Parts makes no representation that materials on this site are
appropriate or available for use in locations outside the territories of
the United States, and accessing them from countries where their
contents are illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this site
from other countries outside of the United States do so on their own
initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws. PRICING INFORMATION AND WEBSITE ERRORS. All
pricing on this website is subject to change. Essex Parts
reserves the right to correct any price error or product detail without
penalty and refuse or cancel any order placed for any product that may
be affected by price or description error, discontinuation or for order
totals which are calculated incorrectly. By using this website you agree
to the understanding that Essex Parts cannot guarantee order
fulfillment under these conditions. The content on this website
has been provided by third parties and manufacturers, by using this site
you understand and agree that Essex Parts is
not responsible for the accuracy provided by those sources and
© 2020 Essex Parts. All Rights Reserved.
